Many block deals have also been seen happening on the other side,
Sumit, pay attention to which ones, see
block and brokerage, there were two big buzzes
in the market today, so the second name is Bal, if we
talk about block deals, then first some
positive, where ICICI Lombard did a
big block deal and it created buzz in the entire insurance
space, be it ICSA
Lombard, II Prudential, SBI
Life, HDFC Life, all of them, there is a good rally in all of them,
a big block
deal has happened around 1, a deal of about 69.7 lakh shares was
seen happening and this deal happened
in the block window this morning, so the details will come this evening,
who participated in it,
but after this big block, a good rally was seen happening in the
entire insurance sector including ICL Lombard, on the
other hand, a big jump of 10 per cent was seen in Railtel
also after the block,
a block deal of around 32 to 33 lakh shares was seen happening here,
which was equity around 1 per cent and the
total value of this block deal is
around Rs 152 crore.  So if
a big block happened in the stock this morning for ₹ 2 crore,
then it is important to believe that such a rise, it is
important to have a block here at this price,
that is why a good rise was
seen there. The third one was already decided, the
block of CMS Info, which was seen
happening in the block window. It was being
speculated earlier that this block would happen.
CNBC had also mentioned the news first that
an equity deal has happened on 28. Around 45
crore shares have changed hands.
This block deal of around 50 crore was seen happening. It will
also be important that
who is participating in this block this evening,
but after this block, there is a slight
negative impact here, but otherwise, a
positive impact was seen in the rest.
Thank you Sumit for the information on this and for
giving details of all the blog posts. C
Info System is on your screen and Meanwhile
Hata had talked about IT, look at
TCS. Just now Sumit also mentioned
TCS, which is giving an advantage to
Nifty.  And Nifty IT is now
in the trend of day high at 265 points, I am talking about it here